Hi guys
Welcome to Super Serious Boy
In this episode, I’m going to talk to you about recycling.
Do you know the man among men?
leader in industry
a real recycling
It must not be like what you imagined
Now in this ESG environment
Many people are talking about recycling
But recycling can be called a very useful
$$
a career and industry
But if you are an industrial person
You have had one since childhood
The logic of rich industrial manufacturing
Then you will be very suitable to watch this episode
Speaking of more profound ESG
Those who are rich or wealthy
Are you talking about carbon emissions or green emissions?
These are the things that ordinary citizens like us
we can't touch
but
Environmental protection, recycling and air pollution
This is what every little citizen and everyone among us
Things that can be dealt with
So there is a company and they are very smart.
you know next month
This was probably when Wendan pomelo was in abundance.
Whenever Mid-Autumn Festival
Moonlight in front of bed
A family’s barbecue and Wanjiaxiang
looking at the moon
award...
Tinker Bell
For example, I like to collect grapefruit peels.
then dry it
Because it can be used as fire
It's the oil in the grapefruit
It’s just that it’s very flammable
So you just tap the lighter
It can be taken and thrown in when we are camping
Or when we usually light a fire in the wild
You can use it as firewood to burn
But you know that every year after giving birth
These farmers, these fruit growers
You know there are so many of them
tree branch waste
Because we mainly want to harvest the fruit
But this whole tree
There will be some
Old, sick and dead branches
Dense branches
In fact, many fruit farmers will give this at this time.
What about after cutting it off?
before
them
I'll just pile it aside and burn it.
If the Environmental Protection Bureau did not discover it at this time,
That'll be fine
But so you're in a lot of places in south central
You often see many people burning straw
Burnt dead branches of fruit trees
Or burning various things
Then because of this social enlightenment
Reports from the public are becoming more and more enthusiastic.
So now actually many people
It can no longer be burned
Unless he secretly burns it
Let's take these old, weak and broken branches
Where there are many, there must be loveliness
Many trees must have dead branches
But you have to pile it up as fertilizer
In fact, have you ever thought about one?
The problem of floor efficiency
It’s just that your orchard is so big inside.
These fruit trees could have been brought
Plant fruits
But in order to have a regional place
There needs to be a place where they can all be piled up
and then pile it until it rots
piled to pieces
Pile it until it becomes fertilizer
It will take a long time
So today in our factory
Industry from elementary school
The boss who grew up and made a lot of money
They thought of one
smart way
That is, if we collect these things
After crushing it again
make it into wood pellets
is it possible
Turn it into a great material
Wood pellets may be for the general audience
I rarely hear this thing
But it is actually
Many European countries, European and American countries
Very heavy use
They use these remaining materials
and then re-form it into wood pellets
The largest power plant in the UK
Just relying on these discarded wood
unwanted wood
The wood that people leave there may be burned randomly.
Use it to generate electricity
So behind this lovely factory
In fact, their former boss
They just do foaming
To do that foaming, you know you need a boiler.
Boiler needs heating
So in fact, many factories in Taiwan use boilers for heating
They actually use coal
Or use some that are not available and burn them
This behavior is actually not environmentally friendly
It will also cause some air pollution
So this frothy boss
They went abroad to buy these wood pellets
Bring it to burn
Discover, burn, discover
Wow
Carbon neutral and environmentally friendly
Burning efficiency is good
And it burns long enough
Then I want to say
We actually have so many farmers in Taiwan
So many fruit people have these problems
Then why don't we build a production line?
Then come and solve this problem for this fruit farmer.
It’s also carbon neutral
So in this episode
If you are an industrial robot
Maybe he can give you a great inspiration
If you are making machines and machines
You may have many great ideas
If you like camping
This company is like this
Made a camping stove
Then we will tell you
How to make wood pellets
Let's go
Now I'm going to teach you how to recycle
Did you know plastic can be recycled?
PET bottles can be recycled
Gold, silver, copper, iron, aluminum
Everything can be recycled
Branches can now be recycled
But recycling
There will be some recycling standards and methods.
You need to cut it uniformly into
The distance of 100 to 150 centimeters
What about the width?
Just don’t have too many weird things
Usually more than three centimeters
Don't mix some garbage in it
Then you can sell it in bundles and recycle it
Many fruit trees cut dead branches
When you throw it in one place and concentrate it
The ants have reached that time of flying
Or there are a lot of pests and diseases
It becomes their parasitic breeding ground.
But at this time you can put away your old illnesses and dead branches
collect them all
sell it for money
After recycling, it becomes materials like this one by one
Then at this time we will return
A recycling yard-like concept
We just need to put it first
coarse crushing
Then it will look like this inside
That is, you will see that there are thin ones and thick ones.
And then there are these small pieces with big roots inside
and then the next one
Then we're going to grind it into fine pieces
So you can take a look at the entire volume
This is it now
The volume is roughly around my thighs and knees.
About
300kg
But if you look
It's the original piece of wood.
300公斤
Do you know what the concept is?
Probably the concept of a car
So it's making wood pellets
It actually has an important focus
It's just that it's there
Concentrated volume
Concentrated Volume It has several benefits
The first one is
You know when we're burning wood or camping
We will burn the wood slowly and slowly
Then you will find that it is inside
Some places are very resistant to burning
Some wood disappears after being burned
So by then we will be coarsely crushing
When it is time to send it to fine grinding
it has a
A physics concept we learned from junior high school
increase density
It will make it burn more completely
And it will burn evenly
Then there is a lot of water vapor in it
Then also because of passing
Wait for it to be finely crushed
high temperature compression
then remove it
Okay, now after we coarsely crush
We are going to take everyone to crush it carefully
Can't pull
Everyone
Just crush it finely like this.
Have you ever thought about raising guinea pigs in elementary schools?
Look at that bag of sawdust
I remember it cost one or two hundred yuan.
If you want to make wood pellets
It will pass through
High temperature and high pressure extrusion
wood it will produce
natural lignin
It is actually a natural adhesive
No need to go through any chemical process
Resin or glue
Or something weird
add to it
Then what you burned
Pure 100% natural
Does my face look ugly now?
I really want to say why this episode is in
I took this during my summer vacation
If we shoot in winter
Exactly one
camping season
We finished production today
Is there any freshly made?
Produced immediately
You can start group buying now
Everyone can
Have a holiday soon
Take it to the mountains for camping
It is not good
The one in front of me is
Granulator
You haven't thought about it
Change this font to look better
Even the employees feel a little better after seeing it.
Cultivate an employee from a young age
More beautiful
Please ask the factory manager to improve it.
The granulator is actually ours just now
That detail
Then from this spiral feeder
then send it down
After sending it down
inside this rolling contraption
Like squeezing a sausage, you know?
Director Chen is actually very good at this.
Our boss Jingxi Chen
Making machines is awesome
If you are really interested in this
Let’s invite Boss Chen again
Just take this mechanical structure
Let this older generation
Come teach us young people how to do it
At this time, let’s match Liu Bei
I read this book a lot
But there are very few people who actually do it on site
Let him talk to this old soul
What kind of new machines can be produced?
It doesn't sound good to me
Doesn’t feel good
do not run
So there are two molds in it
Traditional Chinese medicine refining elixir
Have you seen it?
They put one first
Take that material
squeeze it squeeze squeeze it
Squeeze it into a long strip
What about after the long strip?
will be placed in one
round round round
On the mold with circular groove
Put that one up
Then I'll get a handle
That handlebar
There's also a round round round round look.
Squeeze it through like this
The circles came out one by one.
What about this method?
The traditional Chinese medicine method I just talked about
is completely different
You can think of the machine as two structures
Roll it long and horizontally
This is also a way to make a circle
But what about this one?
Not using this method
There is a mold next to this one
Show it to everyone
The mold next to it looks like this
So you see mechanical design is very interesting?
Use a different mold
use different actions
do it differently
You can make the same thing
But the energy consumption will be different
Consumables may vary
Make a lot of money from being an elementary school mechanic to growing up
Uncle didn't lie to you
real
You can watch this
Small particles at 70 to 80 degrees
We are now walking along Haohan Slope
Climb all the way up
when it climbs up
Everything will fall into this cooling tower
This cooling tower
That is, you can imagine it
like air cooling
Just bring its temperature all the way down to like room temperature
Like the current room temperature
40 degrees
(I'm going to faint from the heat)
So after air cooling
they'll take it down
Then slowly send it here for packaging
After being packaged into materials
will become what everyone sees on the market
Saw it on online shopping
Wood pellets for these packaging materials
That's how it's made
Next we can take these wood particles with us
Just go camping happily
Wait a minute and we will use this thing to burn it for everyone to see.
Let everyone see
Is it any different from ordinary people’s wooden camping?
It just feels more textured in comparison.
Then you know why wood pellets matter?
it is extremely important
because it was
(Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change)
IPCC
Certified as a material that promotes carbon neutrality
So if today
A company can solve
Problems of local farmers in Taiwan
It can also be carbon neutral
It also allows everyone to have a picnic
BBQ
while camping
Get higher quality enjoyment
We can call this
Just one
Wonders of the industrial world
Are you, as a bitter citizen, at this time?
Must be thinking about it
You talk nonsense
Why is burning things called carbon neutral?
Why is it considered carbon neutral by the IPCC?
Let me explain it to you all
Because when trees grow,
it absorbs carbon dioxide
The carbon dioxide becomes sequestered into
wooden material
because it is completely burned
It's also not the kind of combustion that causes a lot of air pollution
So it puts carbon dioxide back into the atmosphere
And in the middle of this
burn completely
Very important
So if you like nature
it's not like some
It’s a material like SRF
It actually burns
Burning it will actually increase carbon emissions in the atmosphere
This will increase air pollution
But things like wood pellets burn
Can slow down global warming
It can also reduce air pollution
It can also bring you the joy of picnicking
It’s really fun to have a picnic
It is common to mistake wood particles for
Classify it as solid recycled fuel
solid renewable fuel
SRF
But in fact, the main raw materials of SRF
They are all waste from industry and commerce
Plastic materials waste rubber
textile
Or wooden pallets or industrial waste
Or all kinds of waste after the decoration of your home is demolished
And wood particles belong to
Primary solid biomass fuel
Production of the entire raw material
Not chemically processed at all
There are many advantages in using
So when you look at the entire production chain
You won't be able to see it at all
any chemical additives
What are the advantages of these wood particles?
Calorific value is very stable
It is through the process of granulation
Let agricultural surplus materials be used
Homogenization
Homogenization you can think of it as equalizing its
mass material density wood
while it's burning
Allows you to provide very stable heat mass
Compared to solid recycled fuel SRF
It’s because the recycled components are different
So when it burns
The change in calorific value will be very large.
Heat it up, cool it down, and it will burn quickly
It can’t be burned all at once
After these wood particles are extruded at high temperatures
So its density will be
Above the densities of 1.1 and 1.2
Denser than water
Therefore, the water content inside the whole capsule will be very low.
When burning, your calorific value will be high.
Thermal energy is also relatively very stable
So it is not only resistant to burning
And its size is very small
You don’t have to carry big and small bags up the mountain
It burned for a while and then disappeared.
Look everyone
Are these wood pellets ready like this?
And what about this?
The bag I’m looking at now is
Pine wood so it can be used in industry
All electricity in Taiwan is generated by this thing.
Let’s learn from the British
This way we won't have a lot of waste
Boss, where is your coat?
No electricity
The ideal is very full
Reality is skinny
Ideal is very cool
Do you know what time it is now?
40 degrees
The weather outside is 40 degrees
So you just treat us as pitiful
Click to subscribe
The front of this one is for industrial use.
But of course it is also used for people’s livelihood.
teak
This is for people's livelihood
Take agricultural materials that would otherwise pollute the air
and then recreate it
Then make it so that it can be burned beautifully
The thermal mass can be very uniform
Used to generate electricity
but you know
This mathematics and science tell us
If you took back all the orchards in Taiwan
In fact, it’s not enough to burn Taipower for a month.
land is too small
But in fact, some countries
I personally highly recommend this government unit
You can start with 5 percent
Or 10 percent
Because you add such things to burn them
it all works
Helps you burn longer
And the homogenization of its heat can be better
so there are some japanese
When they were playing camping
They have a way to play
Just put the wood
Or charcoal
Then when you burn it
Just inside and then add a handful of this
Because this is actually used for camping and civilian purposes.
There are many kinds of flavors
You can make your barbecue flavor
Add a different color
So let’s show you now
How you can use it while camping
Walk
Everyone
Just add a simple package like this
You can send it to Europe
sent to some advanced countries
One kilogram sells to someone for 2, 3, 4, 5 euros
Then make a lot of money
Is it a kind of
Taiwan’s very smart waste wood materials
Reproduced and exported
But if you watched our episode
you can know
In fact, this QUBE
It’s wood pellets made in Taiwan
In fact, it has many different flavors
If you add garlic peel to the wood pellets
The sausage you baked
What you smoked
There will be a garlic smell
And if you take bamboo
There's one underneath it here
Is there bamboo?
There will be a bamboo aroma afterwards
Of course there are many different flavors
what else
litchi
mango
Kucha seeds
All are made from local plants in Taiwan
As a good man who loves his family
There must be one in your home
smoker oven
That is, you can take this wood pellet
Just throw it in there
Then you can adjust the following
the temperature you want
Have you looked at him now
Just wood particles
Eat it in piece by piece
He's eating it piece by piece now.
It's like a small guinea pig
guinea pig monster
This giant guinea pig
The wood particles are corroding it one by one
The guinea pig is hungry at this time
Let's feed it some food
Do you have
Add a little bamboo flavor
but
Bamboo flavor
It seems that for us
This piece of meat from our salmon
Still a little less flavorful
Let's add a little garlic
I'm telling you this
seasoning
Seasoning starts with smoking
Our Sense
It is from the industry of life
Constructed step by step
we want in this
inside of salmon tail
bring a little
Bring a little bit of this lychee fragrance
Bring some lychee
Does this give the lychee vibe?
mixed in this
The aroma of this lychee
I tell you
After the girl took this bite of salmon,
Is it broken??
Then it's basically a smoker
So after you adjust your temperature
Just put what you want to bake
Put it in here
Do you have
So at this time
The taste above is very important
What makes garlic-flavored wood pellets so attractive?
Or are lychee flavored wood pellets more desirable?
Welcome to today's...
But I know
Your poverty limits your imagination
Because this thing is actually quite expensive
This one also costs tens of thousands of dollars
But don't worry, everyone
We have this civilian version
It's just next to the general camping area.
Look, Ameizai has already prepared it for us.
But I know people who go camping
After all, they are still in the minority
So what exactly is this wood pellet?
As a person who likes to cook at home
What can it be used for?
Please look here
QUBE smoke gift box
You know this metal container
What can it be used for?
I tell you
After having this
Become a good family man from now on
Cooking turns a handsome guy into a Thomas
Look at this
So inside if you put
Lychee fragrant
You can smell the fragrance of lychees
You use garlic flavor
You will smell the aroma of garlic
You can make your meat
Add a little flavor at the end
Of course, wood pellets can also be completely
Use directly by burning in the stove
At this time we came to the camping area
Civilian version
GOTRAL
Wood pellet camping stove
Look at the environment where it was just 40 degrees
We're already wet
Now
rain
Isn't it perfect for when it rains?
camping
Picnic
But I guess everyone has been camping.
There should be one
The pain in my heart is the same as mine
every time we go camping
It’s that fire that burns so happily
After burning, you go back to that
your tent or when returning to your car
The smell of smoke is all over my body
Have you seen
Completely smoke-free environment
I'm cooking and frying pork belly at the same time
So what makes this episode special is
We go all the way from industry
Talking about people's livelihood
Speaking of camping
The origin of these things
All are surplus materials from agriculture
Or agricultural materials
It burns people's homes indiscriminately
Bring things that cause air pollution
And now it becomes a kind of
life chain
And what about this stove?
I tell you
It's amazing
it is
Completely designed and manufactured for wood pellets
There are divisions in it
The sizes of the inner furnaces of three different stoves
Three types of combustion tanks
800g  600g  400g
So there are a few in there
three
Suppose you want to cook on a high fire today
Then you can install a larger inner furnace
Inside, it is installed on the Max line.
Suppose it's stormy now
When you are camping in the mountains
Suddenly feel the coldness in my heart
With the cold outside
When you want to put it on fire to keep warm
You can take out the smallest one
and then put it inside
They have a small heater up there just for heating.
What about this little heater?
Completely consistent with its structural design and manufacturing
You can put it on top
Then use wood pellets to light the fire inside.
it won't let your environment
Or create thick smoke around you
It becomes heating
The whole body looks like smoked human flesh
There are several ways to burn a camping stove
One is that you can use alcohol ointment
add it in
You can also use tinder
Or use whatever you can imagine
Ways to make a fire while camping
What is the method we use now?
It's actually an alcohol paste
Then after lighting it up
You have this little fan next to you
Turn it to 2 or 2.5
It looks a lot like a gas stove, right?
But actually underneath it is a kind of
Built-in fan
Throughout the entire industrial manufacturing process, we
The density has been compressed to a tight level
So if you guys like it
Play that game of drilling wood to make fire
Or someone who likes to make fires
You will know that in the beginning when the fire is burning
The kind you want to burn is small hay
Something thinner
Then if it has been
After high temperature extrusion
When the density is about 1.1~1.2
while it's burning
It requires an internal fan underneath
to help it burn
Do you have
So you can just use it for cooking
And have you discovered
When I'm cooking
The pot is now hot
No smoke at all
So if you live in an ordinary building today
You live on the fifth or sixth floor or the seventh or eighth floor
That means you want to heat yourself on the balcony of the building
Occasionally pan-fried pork belly
Feel the atmosphere of this barbecue
If you want to light a fire on your balcony
Do you use a stove like this?
You don’t have to worry about being complained by your neighbors upstairs
Because there is no smoke
Of course, apart from this wok,
It just sells some different accessories.
this
GOTRAL auxiliary hob
What about this auxiliary stand?
it's just the same
It can be placed very stably on your desk
Then you can see the design with a disk in the middle
So it helps your fire
If you want to cook a pot today
Or you want to make corn chowder
it can
Helps the fire to spread evenly
That's less likely to burn
Like if you suddenly want to be on the balcony today
When frying a pan-fried pork belly
I don’t want to spray this fumes into my home.
Yes or no
It's that simple and convenient
It's that simple
Come on, now let's say it's burned out
It looks like this inside
If you want to go home today
You can hold your hand like this
Just take away the burned items.
So what about burning these little scraps?
You can find a metal bucket
Throw it into the dust bin
Then pour it in like this
Then or maybe
You can camp next door
Just dig a small hole
then turn it into compost
Just bury it in it
Remember to extinguish the fire source completely
So during the entire use process?
No need to use fireproof mat on the floor
because underneath itself
It has isolated it
And then it's like we just cooked
Then I made pork belly and used hot pot
Then there is this handle next to it
So actually
The heat protection is pretty good
very safe
So have you ever imagined
It was originally agricultural surplus materials.
but it is now
After directly making it into wood particles
it becomes something a lot like
Life is like a production chain
Things that people didn’t want originally
Then it can be used to generate electricity for industrial use
Then it can even be used while camping
Give you a different sense of life
Follow me while camping
Can solve the previous tradition
Just like wood, charcoal
The problem of producing a lot of smoke
And with this special wood pellet burning stove
this pack
You can probably burn one
five hours to ten hours
It depends on your fuel barrel
Use how big or small
So it's calculated evenly
it's a Bivaska stove
What better than charcoal
Or burn wood?
Even cheaper
So is it in this episode?
You get to know something again
How to reuse new materials
wood pellets
Because it is biomass energy among renewable energy sources
So it can not only take
Fire roasted
smokey
Even the production of electricity
What about its application?
I believe that in the future world
will become more and more widespread
Okay, that’s it for this episode.
If you like our introduction to this episode
You can subscribe to our channel
Or join our membership
You can also join us this time
A very special group buying operation
Because I think
This whole thing is a cool thing
Take things that others don’t want
because of another idea
And then make it into an industrial process?
Then it becomes a way to change many human lives
So this time our channel is exclusive to members
Just spend 60 yuan
money for a drink
Join us as a member
you can get this thing
!Limited time!
Its the lowest price group purchase in Taiwan
This is also what we achieved in a very short period of time
and then be able to give
Small benefits for long-term support of our members
So take advantage of now
It’s not really the peak camping season yet
Hurry up and prepare this kind of thing first
Because during the real camping season
This is how the market is
When everyone needs this thing
Everyone will sell it very expensively
So you can take advantage of now
Before the actual camping begins
Hurry up and buy it at home first
Wait until you're camping
Will not be out of stock easily
Then if you come back again, you won’t be overpriced by others.
Or it won’t be the whole thing again
In the middle of a huge brawl at the camping market
to hurt your wallet
Okay, I've talked too much
This is a super serious boy
See you next week. Bye.
Will my rumor be obvious?
Yoyo: Quite obvious
Pretty obvious?
Or should I flatten it a little bit?
You shouldn't be able to feel it
I'll be blowing air and filming at the same time
Hello everyone who is a member of the super serious channel.
Where is our super serious Costco this month?
The products provided include these